https://www.graftons.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Search
Bag (0)
Recently Added Items
You have no items in your bag.
Trade Privacy Policy
At Grafton International, we are committed to protecting the privacy and security of our customer and site visitors.
Our Privacy Policy explains which personal data we collect from you, or what is provided to us on websites operated by Grafton International Ltd.
The data controller – the company that is responsible for your privacy is Grafton International Ltd. Registered company number 328597.
If you have any questions about how we Protect Your Privacy, drop us a line at dataprotection@graftons.co.uk
How We Use Your Information
We use your information in several way, what we do depends on the information.
Your name and contact details
How we use your name & contact details
Why?
Deliver your orders
In order to fulfil our contract with you
Sending you information by email or post, about our new products and services
To keep you up to date. We only send this with your permission
Fraud prevention and detection
To prevent and detect fraud against either you or Graftons.co.uk
Showing you Graftons.co.uk and Brand adverts as your browse the web
So you can see our latest products and deals
Finding out what you, and other customers, like
To ensure we are giving you what you want to personalise your experience
Your date of birth information
How we use your date of birth
Why?
Fraud prevention and detection
To prevent and detect fraud against either you or Graftons.co.uk
Your payment information
How we use your payment information
Why?
Take payment, and process refunds
In order to fulfil our contract with you
Fraud prevention and detection
To prevent and detect fraud against either you or Graftons.co.uk
Your contact history with us
What you’ve said to us — for example, over phone, email or on social media.
How we use your contact history
Why?
Provide customer service and support
In order to fulfil our contract with you
Train our staff
So that, when you contact us, you get the best possible customer service
Purchase history and saved items
What you’ve bought and what you’ve stored in your basket for another time
How we use your purchase history and saved items
Why?
Sell you things
We’ve got to do this to perform our contract with you, so you can complete your transaction online, and make it easy for your if you want to complete your purchase at another time
Provide customer service and handle returns
In order to fulfil our contract with you
Finding out what you, and other customers, like
To ensure we are giving you what you want
Information about your phone or laptop, and how you use our website and app
Information you give us when you browse our site or use our app, including your IP address and device type and, if you choose to share it with us, your location data, as well as how you use our website and app.
How we use information about your phone or laptop, and how you use our website and app
Why?
Improve our website
To give you the best possible shopping experience
Protect our website
To prevent and detect fraud against either you or Graftons.co.uk
Information from accounts you link to us
What we do if you link your Twitter or Facebook accounts to us
How we use information from accounts you link to us
Why?
To enable you to log into our website simply and easily without having to create a specific account
To make it easier for you to use Graftons.co.uk
Your responses to surveys, competitions and promotions
How we use your responses to surveys, competitions and promotions
Why?
Run the promotions, competitions and surveys
In order to fulfil our contract with you. If you enter a competition, we need to contact you to notify you if you have won.
If you do not wish to share your personal information, you don’t have to, and we respect that. However, you may not be able to buy from the site and receive the best customer experience from Grafton International Ltd.
We anonymise and aggregate personal information (so that it does not identify you) and use it for system administration, data analysis and improving our websites.
We collect and store all data in compliance to the Data Protection Act 1998 and Electronic Communication [EC Directive] Regulations 2003, in addition to the new General Data Protect Regulation which comes into effect from 25th May 2018.
Sharing Your Information
We do not sell any of your personal data to any third party, this includes your name, address, email address or payment information.
However, we share your data with the following companies to carry out our services to you:
Companies within Grafton International
Companies that that help us fulfil your order, such as payment service providers, warehouse, order, packers and delivery companies
Professional service providers such as web and marketing agencies.
Social media platforms if approved by you, to help your login to your account with ease
We may also provide third parties aggregated data which is anonymised for analytical information. We do not disclose information about identifiable individuals
Marketing Messages
If you have given us permission, we will provide you with marketing messages by email and post which we may interest you.How to stop marketing messages from Graftons.co.uk
You can stop receiving marketing messages from us at any time.
Login into your account dashboard
Click on subscriptions
Simply uncheck the subscription box
Alternatively, you can unsubscribe from our mailing list via the link
You can also contact our Customer Service Team via phone, email or post:
You can update your preferences to ensure that you do not receive any further marketing messages, this process may take up to 5-7 working days.
Seeing Adverts for Graftons.co.uk Online
You may see Grafton International adverts online, we use a range of ad technology such as pixels, ad tags and cookies, as well as services offered by social networks such as Facebook, Instagram and Twitter.
Keeping Your Information
We store your information securely as long as your account exists, or as long as required to fulfil our terms of contract to you, and for as long as necessary to provide support related reporting and analysis.
Your Rights
You have the right to ask how your data is being used
You have the right to be request for personal information we hold about you
You have the right to request for information to be amended if inaccurate. This can also be amended online via your web account
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes
You have the right to complain to the your data protection regulator, the Information Commissioner’s Office.
You can exercise the right at any time by contacting us
Changes To How We Protect Your Privacy
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.
Cookie
We use cookies on our website, please see here for further information on our Cookie Policy.
How To Contact Us
If you have any questions about how we use your data, please contact our Customer Service team on:
Email sales@graftons.co.uk
Phone 01827 280 080
Address Grafton International 301 Relay Drive Tamworth
Staffordshire B775PT
This Privacy Policy was published on 16.05.18.
Terms & Conditions
Close
Newsletter
Sign Up for Our Newsletter:
Subscribe
01827 280 080
Explore Graftons
Our Story
World Of
News
Training
Meet The Team
Explore Our Brands
© 2019 Grafton International Ltd. All rights reserved Registered company number 3279497 at Grafton International LTD, 301 Relay Business Park, Tamworth, B77 5PT, England.
Explore Our Brands
Notify me when back in stock
Email Address *
Notify Me
Grafton International supply only extraordinary health and beauty brands for Professionals and Retailers, since 1985. As a leading professional beauty supplier, our products range from professional gel nail polish and nail polish, bath & body care, eyelash extensions and professional waxing products. We bring you the products that work from the brands we love including ibd, ORLY, Carmex, Kneipp, Gigi, Rose & Co, Skin Republic and many more. Create your account online today. Order your health and beauty supplies online today, free delivery on orders over £100 and we offer next day delivery. Alternatively contact our Customer Service team on 01827 280 080.
